FACUNDO MARILAO

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

I have more than 13 years as an entrepreneur in the travel and tourism sector leading and managing a middle size company giving me a broader vision of business and the ability to work as a team. Although I do not have work experience in the IT industry, im looking for an opportunity to apply my professional experience in which I was always passionate.

SKILLS

- -JavaScript
- -HTML + CSS
- -Material UI
- -React + Redux
- -NodeJs
- -ExpressJs
- -PostgreSQL
- -MongoDB
- -SCRUM
- -Git

SOFT SKILLS

- -Teamwork
- -Time management
- -Decision-making
- -Creativity
- -Communication
- -Adaptability
- -Critical thinking

CERTIFICATES

- -Cisco CCNA1 | CCNA2 | CCNA3
- -NDG Linux Unhatched ES 0420
- -Cybersecurity (Cisco Netacad)
- -User Experience

LANGUAGES

- -Spanish: Native
- -Engligh: B2 Upper Intermediate
- -Portugues: Basic

CONTACT

facundomarilao@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/fmarilao www.github.com/fmarilao



EDUCATION

Bootcamp soyHenry

Full Stack Developer | Nov 2020 - Mar 2021

- HTML/CSS/GIT/Javascript Fundamentals
- Advanced Javascript | Data Structure |
 Algorithms
- Advanced DOM/CSS Avanzado | ES6 | AJAX |
 Modules + Bundlers
- React | Redux | DMBS, SQL, ORM.

Instituto Teclab

Associate Degree Software Development Jun 2020 - Jun 2022

- HTML, CSS, Java | SQL and ORACLE databases
- Product design focused on the end user: Design thinking, Agile UX and Lean UX.
- Software quality evaluation with unit tests | Authentication and access control services
- Software lifecycle and project management
- Java and Android mobile programming. Android Studio and AVD SDK
- Creation of apps Material Desing and Responsive desing.



PROJECTS

Ecommerce (Stack PERN)

JavaScript, PostgreSQL, ExpressJs, NodeJs, React, Redux, Material UI

https://github.com/fmarilao/ecommerce

Henry Labs

JavaScript, PostgreSQL + MongoDB, ExpressJs, NodeJs, React Native, React, Redux, Material UI

https://github.com/fmarilao/HenryLabs



EXPERIENCE

Dakar Turismo

Fundador | Octubre 2008 - Diciembre 2020

Managerial and administrative tasks Negotiation with suppliers and customers Management of work teams Tourist groups guide

Fuel station in Pto. Caleta Paula (Argentina)

Networking Lan/Wan | Apr 2005 - Mar 2006

UTP and Fiber Optic installation